Henry Hadlow Designer

I'm a designer and product strategist. I like creating digital services people want to use. Right now I'm working on gov.uk/performance – improving public services using data.

My work is a mix of design, strategy, user research and getting ideas across. Awards include Design of the Year and a D&AD Black Pencil. I also like to play the accordion.

www.manofscience.co.uk henry@manofscience.co.uk

Experience

August 2012 – present Government Digital Service Designer

August 2011 - August 2012 seditionart.com Lead designer

July 2010 - August 2011 The Partners Designer

January-July 2009 Inventory Studio

Summer 2008 Lloyd Northover, Hong Kong

Summer 2007
The Team, London

June 2005 – July 2006 International Pharmaceutical Strategies and Solutions, Berlin Clinical Trial Analyst

Education

2007-2010 Central Saint Martins BA Graphic Design First Class Honours

2003-2005, 2006-2007 University of Bath BSc Natural Sciences First Class Honors City & Guilds Licentiateship

2002 - 2003 London Metropolitan University Foundation Art & Design Distinction

1995 – 2002 Dulwich College, London A-levels: 4×A GCSEs: 8×A★, 3×A

YAwards

Design Museum Design of the Year 2013 for GOV.UK

D&AD Black Pencil for GOV.UK

Cannes Design Lions 2011
Gold for GO RED!

Creative Review Annual 2011
Best in Book for GO RED!

Art Director's Club 2011 Bronze for GO RED!

D&AD 2011
In Book for GO RED!

D&AD Student Annual 2009 In Book for Drinking Straw / Drinking Fountain

